Naked by these at the store already
这些已经在商店裸体了
Cooked
熟
Ok what is
好的，那是什么
Pink nails
粉色指甲
Can I fill an Avengers film
我可以给复仇者联盟补片吗
The outside
在外面
Trying to think of what method One cause me a chat my fingers off
试图思考用什么方法让我闲聊
I'm going to do with my hands
我要用手做
Why are there so many left
为什么还剩下那么多
Doesn't seem to be cooperating with me to well
似乎并没有与我合作
That was a nice
很好
How do I export an area
如何出口区域
Now time to intervene this bad boy
现在该干预这个坏男孩了
How do you get rid of these engines
您如何摆脱这些引擎
I'm going to cut it open
我要把它切开
I see the van
我看到货车
Minerals
矿产
Feels like glass that is so weird
感觉像玻璃一样奇怪
Yeah I've no idea what I'm doing
是的，我不知道我在做什么
Reveille the shrimp poop well you know them
Reveille虾便便，你知道吗
I don't know how to do it
我不知道该怎么做
Ok I can do this
好吧，我可以做到
Slip along the back
沿后滑
Can you pull the tail off
你能把尾巴拉下来吗
Turn the lights to Teal just pull for just have a pension
把灯转到蒂尔（Teal），只领取退休金
So now what
那么现在怎么办
This is the day it's blue it looks like our veins that's would you want to eat some people
这是蓝色的日子，看起来就像我们的静脉，你想吃一些人
Call Graham
给Graham打电话
Big favour
大忙
Put down through the back
放下背部
Oh look it's coming out
哦，看起来出来了
Who are is
谁是
Is
是
I'm kosher so
我很犹太
I'm going to say no
我要说不
Sorry
抱歉
Compare two methods with the more traditional why you want to start by grabbing here
将两种方法与更传统的方法进行比较，为什么要从这里开始
And then working away
然后工作
Around the strip
围绕地带
From the feet on one side
从一侧的脚
Sophie on the other and just feeling that back we can leave the Tail on
另一方面，Sophie只是觉得回来我们可以离开尾巴了
For something like this room packed in or we can simply just sort of picture of the tail
对于像这样的房间挤满东西，或者我们可以简单地只是尾巴的图片
Mpl back
MPL回来
And remove the telephone this year
并今年取下电话
Paring knife
削皮刀
Come through the paradise directly on the backside of the shrimp and asking to review up the van here which you can see
直接穿过虾背上的顶部，并要求在这里查看，您可以看到
This is the digestive tract of the shrimp and then
这是虾的消化道，然后
Just like that for the second letter of your stream sideways on your work surface
就像流中的第二个字母在工作面上横向倾斜一样
Come in with the blade facing away from you
刀片朝外进入
And you're going to both peel back
而且你都将剥离
And slice
和切片
At the same time
与此同时
So appealing their shell
所以吸住他们的壳
Error opening up the digestive tract
错开的打开消化道
I'm just pulled a vein
我只是被拉了一条静脉
Searching for sweetness
寻找甜味
Can you divert
你可以转移
Meaning of shrimp
虾的意思
I'm done
我受够了
Tell me DVLA
告诉我DVLA